剧情回顾...
Previously on Lost...
-你们是谁?   -我们坠机了
-Who are you?  -We crashed here.
815航班?
Flight 815?
你在后舱?
You were in the back?
退后
Back up!
来人
Coming out!
没事了
Everything is cool,
我们谈过了  他们相信我们也是飞机上的
we had a talk and they believe we were on the plane, too.
我想我们能一起去告大洋航空公司了
Guess we can all sue Oceanic together.
你们有几个幸存者?
How many of you survived?
23个
Twenty-three of us.
记得你说过你们有23个人幸存
I thought you said there were 23 of you?
以前是的
There were.
已经过了四天了
It's been four days.
这并不像你想象的那么长
You know, that's not that long.
他们说过可能需要两周的时间来找到洋流
It could take two weeks to find a current.
我是说Michael知道应该怎么做
I mean, Michael knew what he was doing.
我想事情会...
I doubt anyhting...
怎么了?  怎么了?
What? What?
Sun  怎么了?
Sun, what's wrong?
我的结婚戒指不见了
My wedding ring. It's gone.
你不会打算穿这件吧?
怎么了?
我喜欢这双鞋
我也很喜欢...
但是你要穿这样的
他可能比你矮...
这太荒唐了  妈妈
如果你在大学里就能找个丈夫
我们现在就不需要媒人了
我进大学是为了拿学位的
大学四年之后  你的魅力随着你的年龄下降了
你难道就不想在魅力丧失前
找一个丈夫么?
我会在时机成熟的时候找一个丈夫的
你爸爸说现在时机已经到了
我告诉你  伙计
今年
爱情会降临到你的头上
既然算命的书都这么说了  那一定是真的了
我奶奶就是靠这本书找到我爷爷的
它一向很准
是怎样一个女人?
我是说她长得怎样? 这样当我们见面时我就可以认出她了
橙子
是啊  爱情就会像是橙子一样
我照顾不了一个女人
我甚至连自己也管不好
你能让女人来照顾你
那不是一个男人会做的事
男人需要一个生命的目标
他要比任何人都努力工作 然后得到晋升
他就不会像渔民的孩子那样让别人看不起
这只是一个面试  Jin
一个很重要的面试
我看起来怎样?
很棒  是么?
是的  很棒
你忘了把标签剪下来了
你在开玩笑吧?
如果我把标签剪下来了 这要我怎么还掉啊?
这条领带可值钱了
那么  Jin
如果你的爱情找上门来了我该怎么做?
就叫它等一等
伙计
man.
没事吧?   在想Sun?
It's OK?  Sun?
你会再和她团聚的
You'll be with her again.
快了
Soon.
知道了吗?
OK?
我想他们正在考虑怎么处置我们
I think they're trying to figure out what to do with us.
我想他们准备吃了我们
I think they're gonna eat us.
好了 你们全起来
All right, all of you, get up.
我们准备出发了
We're moving out.
出发去哪儿?
Moving out where?
你们得帮我们找水和食物
You're gonna help us get food and water.
什么  我们现在成你们手下了?
What, we work for you now?
你们得照做  因为我们还有很长一段路要走
You're gonna do it because we have a long walk ahead of us.
这么远去哪儿?
A long walk where?
回到你来的地方去
Back to where you came from.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对：Singa后期：xyz 双语制作：闲逛
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
没有情况
All clear.
-Mike  我想我们得找机会逃走  -是么?
-Mike, I thinkwe ought to stage a prison break here.  -Yeah?
在我弄明白这到底发生了什么之前
I want to figure out what the hell's going on here
我是不会做任何决定的
before I make decisions about anything.
好了  大家听一下
OK, people, listen up.
我们得收集尽可能多的食物和水
We need to gather as much food and water as we can.
两人一组行动
We travel in pairs.
你们得尽可能跑快一点  别发出任何声音
You move as fast as you can. Don't make any noise.
也许你能花几分钟时间来向我们解释一下
Maybe you could just take a minute to explain to us
到底发生了什么事情让你们如此紧张?
what the hell is going on over here that's got you all so on edge?
你知道么?  这倒是个好主意
Know what? That's a great idea.
也许我们能在路上互相讲故事
We can swap stories on the road.
在出发前我们先去探探路
I'm going to go scout before we move.
Cindy  和他一起去
Cindy, go with him.
Libby  去看看你能找到哪些水果
Libby, see what fruit you can gather.
把他带上
Take him with you.
他叫Michael
His name is Michael.
是的  好  Michael
Yeah. Right. Michael.
-等等  -我没事的  伙计  别担心
-Wait  -I'll be OK, man, don't worry.
Bernard和我去抓鱼
Bernard and I will gather the fish.
鱼
Fish.
他知道怎么抓鱼
The man knows how to fish.
如果我是你我就带上他
I'd take him with you if I were you.
好  他也和我们一起去
Fine. He comes with us too.
Sun
你没事吧?
You OK?
我的结婚戒指不见了
I lost my wedding ring.
你最后一次看到是什么时候?
When was the last time you saw it?
我戴习惯了  我不...
I'm so used to it, I don't...
我不知道
I don't know.
我有一次也丢了结婚戒指
I lost my wedding ring once.
当你很想找到某样东西的时候你会很疯狂
It's crazy where you'll look when you want to find something bad enough.
翻遍屋子外的垃圾桶
I went through the...the garbage outside the house
翻空垃圾袋和其它垃圾
emptied the bags and everything.
我甚至把浴室里的水管也锯开了
I even took apart the pipes in my bathroom
因为我确信它掉在了排水沟里
because I was convinced that it had gone down the drain in the sink.
你妻子怎么说?
What did your wife say?
-她不会知道的  -为什么?
-She never knew.  -How is that?
我去宝石商那里要了一个复制品  就是这样
I went to a jeweller and I had a replica made, that's how.
现在它正呆在我家空空荡荡的袜子柜里
Yeah, now it's just rattling around in my sock drawer back home.
我能帮你找
I can help you look.
不  谢谢
No. Thanks.
我肯定它会出现的
I'm sure it will turn up.
你想过来帮帮我们么?
You wanna help us out over here?
你想吃东西么?
You wanna eat?
来帮帮我们
Help us.
(韩语)
我看起来会说韩语么?
Does it look like I speak Korean?
鱼
Fish.
你在阿珊娜酒店工作过
是的  先生
做餐馆工?
我升为服务员了  先生
但他们不在内部提拔
是的  先生  不多见
我相信我是少数的几个例外
你是哪个乡的?
什么?
你明显不是城里人
你是哪个乡的?
纳曼尼  在南海岸
怪不得...
我想我闻到你身上的鱼腥味了
这东西露出来了
谢谢  先生
Kwon先生被录用了
你马上可以开始工作了
不论晴雨你都得工作
别想要加薪或是休假
还有  Kwon先生
汉城之门
是全国最好的酒店
如果有像你一样的人进来
就别开门
好的  先生  我懂了
我会尽力工作的  谢谢
-对不起  Micheal  -什么对不起?
-Sorry, Michael.  -Sorry about what?
关于...把你和你的朋友扔进坑里的事
You know, about...throwing you and your friends into the pit.
-朋友...  -怎么了?
-Friends...  -What?
只是不认为他们是朋友
I never thought about them like that.
我是说  其中一个是我的朋友
One is my friend.
-我想不是那个乡巴佬  -恩  不是他
-I'm guessing not the redneck.  -Yeah. Not the redneck.
我今生从没见过这么让人害怕的人
I don't think I've ever seen someone so scared in my life.
现在我知道什么叫害怕了
And I know about scared.
这就是为什么你们把我们扔进坑里?
That why you threw us in the pit?
因为你们害怕?
Because you're scared?
至少我们已经...
And we've got...
相互信任了
trust issues.
是这样么?
How about that?
到底哪儿有水果?
Where the hell are all the fruits?
这些树上的都已经被我们摘光了
We've picked these trees clean.
有时你倒能在地上找到几个
Sometimes you find them on the ground.
那么为什么你们不去内陆看看?
Why don't you head inland?
水果全在我们那边了
That's where all the fruit is on our side.
-我们不去那里  -为什么?
-We don't go that way.  -Why?
因为他们就是从那里来的
Because that's where they come from.
在路上防身用的
For your protection when we travel.
是你做的?
You made this?
你叫什么名字?
So what's your name, anyway?
Mr Eko.
Eko先生?
Mr Eko?
是的
Yes.
怎么会这样  就像是ED先生
So, what's that like Mister Ed?
-Michael走了  -什么?
-Michael left.  -What?
他说了些什么后就冲进了丛林
He just said something and he went into the jungle.
他走了
He's gone.
快点  我们马上离开
Let's go. We're leaving now.
你说我们离开是什么意思?
What do you mean?
你的伙伴跑进丛林里去了
Your buddy ran off into the jungle.
Michael...他走了
Michael... left.
他想说什么?
What's he saying?
Walt!
等等  有只收音机
Wait, you have a radio?
能用么?
Does it work?
你会用么? 多好的一个主意啊
Can you use it? What a great idea.
-你要拖我们后腿?  -不  Michael
-You gonna slow us down?  -No! Michael.
在他告诉他们我们在哪儿之前我们得离开
We're leaving before he can tell them where we are.
Michael
我们能怎么做  等他?
What are we supposed to do? Wait for him?
没找到他孩子他是不会回来的
He ain't comin' back without his kid.
Walt  在找到Walt前他是不会回来的
Walt! He ain't comin' back without Walt.
你真的以为他能找到?
You really think he's gonna find him?
也许你还没注意到  人人都在为自己着想
In case you haven't noticed, it's every man for himself, Chewie.
Mike只担心他自己
Mike's gotta worry about Mike
我也只需要管好自己
and I gotta worry about me.
等等
Wait.
拜托
Please.
你走错路了
You're going the wrong way.
他是往那边去的
That's where he is going.
向着他们
Toward them.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我要跟他一起去找他的朋友
I am going to help him find his friend.
我们不能在这儿等你
We can't wait for you.
我没期望你们等我
I don't expect you to.
你得一步一步回忆
All you gotta do is retrace your steps.
就像...你昨天做了什么?
Like, what did you do yesterday?
我醒来  洗漱
I woke up. Washed up.
和Shannon散步
Walked with Shannon.
我们摘了些水果...
We picked some fruit,
喂了Vincent  然后...
cut it up to feed Vincent. Then I was...
你喂过狗了?
Whoa. You fed the dog?
这就是了
Bingo.
那么...汉城
So...Seoul.
是在韩国还是朝鲜?
Is that in the good Korea or the bad Korea?
在韩国
The good one.
你去看奥运会了么?
Did you go to the Olympics?
Hurley  这太荒唐了
Hurley, this is ridiculous.
在这儿等...
Waiting here for...
这狗没吃我的戒指
The dog did not eat my ring.
伙计  狗什么都吃
Dude, dogs will eat anything.
当我还是个孩子  我有只狗Buster
When I was a kid, my dog Buster...
我会把零钱都存在一个抽屉里
I had this drawer where I'd throw in all my change.
当不见了之后我以为有人偷了
I guess there were Smarties in there.
然而一天后  Buster拉出了1元35分
So the next day, Buster craps out a buck thirty-five in nickels.
你养过狗么?
Did you ever own a dog?
是的
Yes.
Jin给过我一只
Jin gave me one.
一只小狗
A puppy.
它叫什么
What was his name?
Bpo
-有什么意义么?  -嗯  意思是"一个吻"
-That mean something?  -Yes. It means "a kiss".
一个吻
A kiss.
把手保持在膝盖上  好么?
除非别人直接和你讲话  否则别开口
她真漂亮啊
你会爱上他的
他很英俊...受过良好的教育...
这家酒店和其它12家酒店都是他家开的
下午好  欢迎来到汉城之门
你的酒店真是漂亮
哦  你太客气了
我知道你女儿上过汉城国立大学
当然比不过哈佛了
好吧
让我们留点时间给他们两个认识一下吧
那么谁给你的压力较大?
你妈妈还是你爸爸?
当然是我爸爸了...通过我的妈妈
你呢?
我的爸爸  通过我的妈妈
姑妈  还有奶奶
你是学什么的?
艺术历史
老实说我对艺术一点也不了解
你学什么?
中世纪的俄国文学
但是最后我还是学了酒店管理
是啊  不知不觉
我通常都很不喜欢这样的会面
但是今天...却不同
对我来说也一样
-别去    -Michael
-No!    -Michael!
等等  别去
Wait! No!
他叫Goodwin
His name was Goodwin.
其他人?
Others?
Michael?
不是
No.
可以治你的伤
For your cut.
你结婚了吧?
So, you're married?
你的戒指
Your ring.
你有妻子?
You have a wife?
是的
Yes.
你呢?
You?
比你惨
Worse.
你的妻子
Your wife
她叫什么?
what is her name?
她叫什么名字?
Her name?
Sun
她和你一起
She was with you?
在飞机上?
On the plane?
糟糕的一天?
Bad day?
是干净的
It's clean.
谢谢
Thank you.
不介意我坐下吧?
You mind if I sit?
你看到了?
Did you see me?
糟蹋你的菜园?  没有
Rip apart your garden? No.
有时我希望我有个花园来让我糟蹋
Sometimes I wish that I had a garden to tear apart.
我想我没看过你发火
I don't think I have ever seen you angry.
我以前经常发火
Oh, I used to get angry.
总是
All the time.
也很失落
Frustrated, too.
那么你现在不失落了?
So you are not frustrated anymore?
我不再失落了
I'm not lost any more.
你怎么做到的?
How did you do that?
就像塞翁失马焉知非福...
Same way anything lost gets found.
我不再期望什么了
I stopped looking.
下午好  Lee先生
不介意我借用一下它吧?
我有个约会
当然  先生
谢谢
你叫..
Jin Soo Kwon  先生
谢谢  Kwon先生
然后那张卡滑到了门外面...
而我在走廊上  身上只有一条毛巾
我想那是电影里经常有的情节
我得和服务员说这家酒店是我开的
但她不相信我
真是尴尬
我不敢相信你是这么的...平易近人
我认为你也很出色  Sun
那么...
我很想让我们继续保持联系
我们的父母肯定都会很高兴的
不再有媒人  不再有压力
我们能轻松了
让我告诉你个秘密吧
好的
我在哈佛的时候认识了一个美国女人
我还没告诉过我的爸爸  但是...
六个月后  我就要搬去那儿和她结婚了
等等...你不认为...
当然很好
美国
真是好地方
我认为你...
我很为你高兴
下午好  先生
你还需要点什么么?
不  不用了  谢谢
要点咖啡或是点心么?
不了  谢谢
事实上  我还有个约会
Sun...
非常感谢你的午餐
不  不是那边  是这边
No, not that way. Over here.
是脚后跟
Around here
还很新
This is fresh.
这些痕迹
His tracks.
Michael?
是的  Michael
Yes, Michael.
他们是不会留下痕迹的
They don't leave tracks.
-Michael...   -不
-Michael...   -No.
他们没有抓他
They don't have him.
他们是从那儿来的
They came from that way.
你的朋友往那儿去了
Your friend went that way.
刚好避开他们
Crossed ahead of them.
很幸运
Very lucky.
你...回去  我去
You... go back. I go.
不
No.
我们一起去
We go together.
不好意思  不好意思
能让我的小孩用一下洗手间么?
拜托  先生  他尿急
对不起先生  只对酒店客人开放
街的那一头有厕所
能忍住么?
抱歉  他真的很急
好的
进去吧  在左边
但是拜托...快一点
谢谢...你真是个好人
快...快去
Kwon先生
我是怎么和你说的  有些人不能进去
我很抱歉  先生
这是对你的第一次警告
那只是一个小孩
他能在排水沟里随便撒尿
你们这些人都是这样的
如果你想保住工作...
找到他们赶他们出去
你做什么?
谢谢你给的机会  先生
你好
Hello.
风景真好
It's pretty.
Hurley告诉我你的结婚戒指不见了
Hurley told me that you lost your wedding ring.
我坐在这里
I was just sitting here
告诉自己为这个事心烦真是愚蠢
telling myself it's silly to be so upset about it.
它只是一样东西
It is just a thing.
他们才刚走了几天  你知道...
They've only been gone a few days, you know...
别说了
Don't.
我厌烦了每个人都和我说他没事
I am sick of everyone saying he is all right.
他肯定出事了
He is not all right!
Claire找到了一个漂流瓶
Claire found the bottle.
里面有我们写的信息
The one with the messages inside.
是竹筏上的
The one from the raft.
瓶子在哪儿?
Where is it?
我埋了
I buried it.
停下
Stop.
把水给我
Can I see your water?
你再拖我们后腿我们就不管你了
Keep slowing us down, we'll leave you behind.
走吧  别管我了
Go ahead. Leaving me behind.
好的  再见
All right, see ya.
我有个问题
Got a question for you.
什么?
Yeah?
既然你的向导走了
Now that your tracker's gone
你没了我怎么还能找到我们的营地?
how are you gonna find our camp without me?
横穿过这个岛  沿着海滩走
Walk across the island, follow the beaches.
并且Eko会回来的
And Eko's coming back.
你结婚了么?
You married?
什么?
What?
你结婚了吗?
Are you married?
没有
No.
太糟了
Too bad
你看起来像结过婚了
you seem suited for it.
真有趣
Funny.
你呢?
What about you?
没有  小姐
No, ma'am.
你是同性恋?
You gay?
真有趣
Funny.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我们还等什么?
What are we waiting for?
在这儿等着
Wait here.
我们跟丢了
We lost his trail.
我再回去找一找
I go back and find it.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
-回去    -Michael
-Go back.    -Michael!
回去  伙计
Go back, man!
Walt  Walt
Walt
-Michael    -走开
-Michael!  -Look, go away!
没找到他我是不会回去的
I'm not going back without him!
Walt  我在这儿
Walt! I'm here!
你在哪儿?
Where are you, man?
Walt
怎么了  你担心他们听到我?
You worried they're gonna hear me?
让他们把我带走
Let them take me!
来吧  来把我带走
Come! Come take me!
这么喊是没用的
Shouting is not a good idea.
你得和我们一起回去
You need to come back with us now.
我不会丢下我孩子不管的
I'm not leaving him out here!
离我远点
Stay away from me!
我知道他们带走了你孩子...
I know they took your son...
但是你不知道这些人有多少能耐
but you have no idea what these people are capable of.
而且如果他们不愿意的话你是找不到他们的
They will not be found if they don't want to be.
他们从我身边活活把孩子抢走了
They took him... right out of my hands.
就从我身边
Right out of my hands!
没找到他我是不会回去的
I'm not going back without him.
你会找到Walt的   Michael
You find Walt, Michael.
我能看看吗?
Can I see it?
Kate  那些是私人信息
Kate, those are private.
Kate  别看了
Kate, stop.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我们没有
We didn't
我没向他说再见
I didn't say goodbye.
Sawyer?
Sun...
噢  对不起
你没事吧?
给
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====